castplatform.com 2013-08-06

# c.a.s.t | Native Advertising

Privacy Policy

We, After Download Ltd., treasure the privacy of the users of afterdownload.com (the "Website") and the users of the our proprietary ad serving platform (the "Platform") and that is why we made every effort to create a service that adopts adequate privacy standards as set forth below. 

Preamble

When you use this Website and/or the Platform, you consent to adhering privacy guidelines which are at least as strict as the privacy guidelines set forth herein. You further expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

WE WILL NOT USE OR SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH ANYONE EXCEPT AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and therefore we ask you to check back periodically the most updated form of Privacy Policy as indicated below. Your continued use of the Platform and/or this Website after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed as your continued express acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended.

Information Collected

Personal Information

We do not collect any information other than information that you explicitly provide and which identifies your personally, such as your name, address, services purchased, payment methods and so on ("Personal Information")

Non-Personal Information

We may collect and aggregate non-identifying information regarding your use of our Website, Platform ad campaigns, advertisements viewed, pages browsed, search inquiries, offers and services that interested you or which you have utilized, the type of browser you are using, your IP address, the URL you have come from and the time spent at that URL, cookies and your domain type and server ("Non-Personal Information")

Use of Collected Information

Personal Information

Personal Information shall be used solely in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under a common control that we have or may have in the future, or such third parties that acquire us or all or substantially all of our assets, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms.

Otherwise, we will not disclose your Personal Information to any third party, unless:

  * Required to do so as part of any legal proceedings conducted between you and the Website
  * Required to do so by court order
  * In case the activity of the Website is transferred to a third party, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms

Non-Personal Information

Non-Personal Information shall be used to ensure the adequate operation, improve, modify, cancel, enrich or adjust the Website and/or the Product, in general or to your area of interest. We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information (in the form collected) to third parties, including, inter alia, potential and actual advertisers, sponsors, business partners, investors, affiliates and consultants, at our sole discretion

Cookies, Web Beacons and other Technologies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a web browser directory by a website or an advertisement related action. There are two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are created temporarily in your web browser directory while you are visiting a website and deleted once you leave the website. The persistent cookies remain in your web browser and are activated again once you visit the website that created that such specific cookie. A web beacon is a small file used by a website or an advertisement related action to keep track of your navigation through a single website or a series of websites A pixel is a small line of code which is used by a website or an advertisement related action to assign online activities to a computer or browser

We use cookies and other technologies in order to ensure proper operation, collect Non-Personal Information and ensure information security. Although our collection of Non-Personal Information does not personally identifies users, we are still committed to giving you and other users the opportunity to exercise choice of opt out from collection of such Non-Personal Information that we collect. For removing cookies and other technologies please refer to the "Your Ad Choices" clause below

Your Ad Choices

Please note that you browser enable you to disable all cookies (if you do not know how to do this, check out the "Help" file of your browser), however, this may interfere with your use of the Website, the Platform or other internet websites

If a user would like to Opt-Out of the non-personally identifying cookies that our Website or Platform may use (directly by us and not by third parties as referred to below), the user can click on the Opt-Out link below

<http://www.afterdownload.com/pages/track>

If you use a new computer, upgrade or change web browsers or take any action which results in the deletion of the "opt out" cookie, you will need to perform this opt-out process again upon any such change

Third Party Advertisements

We may use third-party advertising companies in order to serve advertisements on our Website and/or through our Platform. Such parties may use cookies and/or other technologies placed on users computer in order to adjust the advertisements presented on to them on a certain third parties website. With respect to such third parties activities and cookies please note the following:

  * Such use is subject to the privacy policy of said parties and is not subject to these terms
  * Clicking the 'opt out' option from receipt of our cookies does not automatically allows you to opt out of such third party cookies and you are required to visit such third parties websites in order to opt out of such cookies
  * We do not monitor or control such third parties cookies and accordingly we are not responsible or liable in any manner to the type of information collected by such third parties cookies

Opting out from receiving cookies does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the website or network from which you opted out will no longer deliver advertisements tailored to your preferences and usage patterns

Rules Related to Children's Privacy

Our Website and Platform are not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 as part of the Website and Platform. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a user under the age of 13 as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records.

Information Security

Note that although we take measures to secure the information and reduce the risk of unwanted disclosure, we can not guarantee the information will not be exposed as a result of unauthorized penetration to our servers. If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@afterdownload.com
